http://www.space-electronics.com/privacy-terms-of-use

Privacy and Terms of Use
Space Electronics Is Committed to Protecting Your Privacy.The
following privacy statement describes our practice with respect to the
collection and use of your personally identifiable information (personal
information) on this Web site. Privacy and CookiesNo cookie tracking leading to personally identifiable information is kept without your permission. Space Electronics will not attempt to identify users based on collected Google Analytics information unless forms witth personal data is submitted. The only cookie being used is limited to Google Analytics with precise IP address location indentification turned off. Default cookie functions include the following:    - Tracking use of website from page to page    - Identifying platform as mobile/non-mobile in order to determine how to display content on phones    - Browser detection    - Detecting repeat visitors    - Detecting geographic data: City, Region, Country of Origin    - Language setting     - Campaign tracking visitors from online sources like e-newsletters and online adsSurvey & Form Data PrivacySpace Electronics may require you to provide us with personal information if you would like to participate in some activities available on or benefit from services offered on, this Web site. We endeavor to limit our requests for personal information to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes.By submitting your contact information, you are providing Space Electronics consent to communicate with you by mail, e-mail, and/or phone and to store your information electronically.Depending on your request, Space Electronics shares the information you provide on forms with appropriate individuals located in Space Electronics’ marketing and sales, service, engineering, executive departments and/or with outside sales or service representatives (see this page: https://www.space-electronics.com/Contacts). Also, individuals with passwords at our marketing agency and programmers may access your contact information as part of tabulations, eliminating spam submissions, making certain the programming is working.Also, Space Electronics may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on this Web site, protect and defend the rights or property of Space Electronics or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Space Electronics employees, users of Space Electronics products or services, or members of the public. Space Electronics reserves the right to transfer personal information to third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets. Space Electronics does not otherwise use, sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties.The contact information you provide does not automatically get deleted after some time period as described in the EU GDPR regulations, as of current company policy, since it contains mostly business to business information and it is often from either current or future customers (in request for quotations) which sometimes takes years to end as a sale in large capital goods projects.Edit Contact InformationVisitors from the EU per GDPR (and in
Canada per CASL and California per CCPA) may get their contact information changed. Please email to
with a subject line of “EDIT CONTACT” and include the changes you want to make to your contact information and the reason you need to change it. Note: If you have a prior transactional relationship with Space Electronics we may not be required to change any/all previous instances of the information stored in our files.Also, assuming you do not have a prior transactional relationship with the company, visitors from the EU may contact us per the GDPR regulation to remove their own stored marketing contact information using their previously submitted business email address. Please use the following address,
with a subject line of “REMOVE CONTACT”.Please note that any non-contact information like comments or materials sent to us, including feedback data, are deemed to be non-confidential. We have no obligation with respect to such responses, and Space Electronics shall be free to use, reproduce, distribute and publicly display such comments and materials without reference to you personally. Space Electronics is also free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such responses for any purpose whatsoever unless otherwise specified.Marketing Email Opt-OutSpace Electronics provides you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive emails from us. Navigation ErrorsPlease report navigation errors and other website maintenance problems and/or comments to webmaster@space-electronics.com. We appreciate your assistance in helping us maintain an error-free website.Website DevelopmentThis website was designed and developed by Praxis Communications, Inc., a Philadelphia area BtoB marketing communications firm.
Copyright 2020, Space Electronics LLC
Privacy And Terms Of Use
